[
    {
        "question": "how are you doing?",
        "answer": "We are doin' great homie!"
    },
    {
        "text": "q. How do you comfort a JavaScript bug? a. You console it.",
        "question": "How do you comfort a JavaScript bug?",
        "answer": "You console it.",
        "author": "elijahmanor",
        "created": "09/06/2013"
    },
    {
        "text": "q. Why did the child component have such great self-esteem? a. Because its parent kept giving it `props`!",
        "question": "Why did the child component have such great self-esteem?",
        "answer": "Because its parent kept giving it `props`!",
        "author": "elijahmanor",
        "created": "05/22/2017"
    },
    {
        "text": "q. Why do C# and Java developers keep breaking their keyboards? a. Because they use a strongly typed language!",
        "question": "Why do C# and Java developers keep breaking their keyboards",
        "answer": "Because they use a strongly typed language",
        "author": "elijahmanor",
        "created": "09/23/2013"
    },
    {
        "text": "q. Why did the functional component feel lost? a. Because it didn't know what `state` it was in!",
        "question": "Why did the functional component feel lost?",
        "answer": "Because it didn't know what `state` it was in!",
        "author": "elijahmanor",
        "created": "05/22/2017"
    },
    {
        "text": "q. Why was the JavaScript developer sad? a. Because he didn't Node how to Express himself!",
        "question": "Why was the JavaScript developer sad?",
        "answer": "Because he didn't Node how to Express himself!",
        "author": "elijahmanor",
        "created": "09/10/2013"
    },
    {
        "text": "q. Why did the developer go broke? a. Because he used up all his cache!",
        "question": "Why did the developer go broke?",
        "answer": "Because he used up all his cache!",
        "author": "elijahmanor",
        "created": "09/17/2013"
    },
    {
        "text": "When a JavaScript date has gone bad, \"Don't call me, I'll callback you. I promise!\"",
        "author": "elijahmanor",
        "created": "09/09/2013"
    },
    {
        "text": "Dev1 saw a strange JavaScript function & asked, \"What is this?\". Dev2 responded, \"I don't know. I would've called you, but I was in a bind\"",
        "author": "elijahmanor",
        "created": "09/09/2013"
    },
    {
        "text": "Two JavaScript developers walked into the variable `bar`. Ouch!",
        "author": "elijahmanor",
        "created": "09/10/2013"
    },
    {
        "text": "q. Why did Jason cover himself with bubble wrap? a. Because he wanted to make a cross-domain JSONP request.",
        "question": "Why did Jason cover himself with bubble wrap?",
        "answer": "Because he wanted to make a cross-domain JSONP request",
        "author": "elijahmanor",
        "created": "09/11/2013"
    },
    {
        "text": "q. Why did the software company hire drama majors from Starbucks? a. Because they needed JavaScript experts!",
        "question": "Why did the software company hire drama majors from Starbucks?",
        "answer": "Because they needed JavaScript experts!",
        "author": "elijahmanor",
        "created": "09/12/2013"
    },
    {
        "text": "q. Why did the CoffeeScript developer keep getting lost? a. Because he couldn't find his source without a map!",
        "question": "Why did the CoffeeScript developer keep getting lost?",
        "answer": "Because he couldn't find his source without a map!",
        "author": "elijahmanor",
        "created": "09/13/2013"
    },
    {
        "text": "q. What do you call __proto__? a. Dunder proto q. Michael Scott was the regional manager where? a. __mifflin__",
        "question": "What do you call __proto__? Dunder proto. Michael Scott was the regional manager where?",
        "answer": "__mifflin__",
        "author": "elijahmanor",
        "created": "09/16/2013"
    },
    {
        "text": "q. How did the doctor revive the developer? a. The dev wasn't responsive so the doc picked him up by his bootstraps!",
        "question": "How did the doctor revive the developer?",
        "answer": "The dev wasn't responsive so the doc picked him up by his bootstraps!",
        "author": "elijahmanor",
        "created": "09/16/2013"
    },
    {
        "text": "q. Why did the C# developer fall asleep? a. Because he didn't like Java.",
        "question": "Why did the C# developer fall asleep?",
        "answer": "Because he didn't like Java.",
        "author": "elijahmanor",
        "created": "09/18/2013"
    },
    {
        "text": "q. Why did the JavaScript boxer goto the chiropractor? a. Because his backbone was angular from a knockout and required attention!",
        "question": "Why did the JavaScript boxer goto the chiropractor?",
        "answer": "Because his backbone was angular from a knockout and required attention!",
        "author": "elijahmanor",
        "created": "09/19/2013"
    },
    {
        "text": "q. How did the web dev hurt Comic Sans feelings? a. Once he saw the font he quickly changed to Open Sans and exclaimed \"In your @font-face!\"",
        "question": "How did the web dev hurt Comic Sans feelings?",
        "answer": "Once he saw the font he quickly changed to Open Sans and exclaimed \"In your @font-face!\"",
        "author": "elijahmanor",
        "created": "09/20/2013"
    },
    {
        "text": "q. Why was Ember.js turning red? a. Because it was EMBERrassed for not remEMBERing its route home!",
        "question": "Why was Ember.js turning red?",
        "answer": "Because it was EMBERrassed for not remEMBERing its route home!",
        "author": "elijahmanor",
        "created": "09/24/2013"
    }
]